

PRESTON WANG-STOSUR-BASSETT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

Self-motivated web developer skilled in a variety of languages. Phenomenal communication skills, capable of explaining complex situations in easy to understand terms. Devoted to making the web a better place.

I am twenty-one years old with eight years professional experience developing for the web. Passionate and dedicated to my work, I have an eye for design and talent for computer programming. A self-proclaimed Linux enthusiast who enjoys traveling to far away lands and listening to an expansive variety of music.

CONTACT

- +1 630 677 2884
- p.wanstobas@gmail.com www.stosur.info
- Ann Arbor Michigan, 48197
 United States of America

FOLLOW

o Facebook

facebook.com/sotch.pr35mac

o Twitter

twitter.com/Sotch_pr35mac

o Linked In

linkedin.com//in/prestonstosurbassett

o Github

github.com/sotch-pr35mac

WORK EXPERIENCE

+ MCON Beijing

2016

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Developed WeChat apps for corporate clients in China using Angular and WeUI. Gained valuable experience working in international team using Agile Development Methodology.

+ CPR Cell Phone Repair

2015 - 2016

MANAGER, SALESMAN & TECHNICIAN

Managed the Kalamazoo franchise location, repaired a variety of mobile electronics and increased sales with a "no-pressure" sales style.

+ Floydware LLC

2010 - 2013

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Internationalized software for use in other languages and developed Android mobile app for cloud scheduling software company. Valuable experience working in office setting; acquired coding "good-practives" by developing within a team.

> SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT JAVA PHOTOSHOP

CHINESE NODE.IS VUE.IS

EDUCATIONS

+ Kalamazo College

2014 - 2018

B.S. COMPUTER SCIENCE

Senior studying computer science and Chinese with a 3.6 GPA. Studied abroad one year in China at Capital Normal University in Beijing and Harbin Institute of Technology in Harbin.

+ Glenbard West Highschool

2011 - 2014

HIGHSCHOOL

Enrolled in all honors and AP classes. On high honor roll with a weighted 5.3 GPA. Vice President Chinese National Honors Society. Involved in political science and Chinese clubs.

INTERESTS









